<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Susan Qi</title>
    <link>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Susan Qi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 14:53:03 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Internship</title>
      <link>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 14:53:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/intern/</guid>
      <description>Quantitative Strategy Researcher, XinXiang Asset Management, Shanghai, China May to July 2021
• Executed the high frequency trading strategy with a principal of 8,000 USD in the stock market based on volume &amp;amp; price changes. Earned a total rate of return of 8% in 2 months.
• Quantified the T+0 transaction strategy using Python based on historical order information. Analyzed the opening/closing time based on the sale/buy amounts and prices in each tick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:49:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>I am now an MEng student at Cornell university studying financial engineering. I did mathematics and statistics in my undergraduate school at UIUC. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in using quantitative tools to do price predictions and risk management.
 title: &amp;ldquo;Aboutme&amp;rdquo; date: 2022-05-07T18:08:18-04:00 draft: true </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 22:34:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aquamarine-blancmange-9e1364.netlify.app/posts/projects/</guid>
      <description>Tesla Stock Forecasting feature analysis, ORIE 5741 Big Messy Data, Ithaca, NY Aug. 2021 to Dec. 2021
• Extracted Elon Musk’s Twitter content to conduct sentimental analysis and compared with the price trend one day later. • Conducted logistic regression, neural network and random forest to predict Tesla’s price trend and got an accuracy of 65.5%.
Study on Credit Card Fraud Detection Data, STAT 432 Basics of Statistical Learning, Urbana, IL Dec.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
